The End What's the matter?
There's...
something in my ear.
Can you hear me, Yuji Itadori?
There's no time.
Wait, wait!
I'm your ally, you idiot!
It's Mechamaru from Kyoto!
There's no time.
I'll only say this once.
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
Good night, Satoru Gojo.
Let us meet again in the new world.
Good night or not, it's time
for you to wake up already.
How long are you going to let
it keep using you, Suguru?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Incredible!
This is definitely a first!
Hey, Code!
Mahito, take a look at this.
You once told me you thought the
soul exists before the body does.
But really, the body is part of the
soul, and the soul is part of the body.
There's no other way to
explain this phenomenon,
or the fact that this
body's memories can keep
flowing into my mind even
after I swapped out hosts.
Yeah, but does that have
to be a universal truth?
Because of our techniques, we kind
of live in two different worlds.
So each technique dictates its world.
I like it.
What a lovely idea.
Ugh, come on!
Come on.
Guys, are we going to do this or what?
The view sucks and I'm just kind of bored.
I wanted to enjoy this sight for a
little bit longer, but you are right.
I wouldn't want anything to happen.
Gate close.
so now we can't use this anymore right it
only holds one unless the man inside kills
himself that's all we get oh that's pretty
lame well in any case
the ceiling is complete
I am a special
You are my special The rest
of the world, let's go and run
The world, the world,
let's go and run Oh no,
you know, what it's all about me say again
I love it baby
die you are all love I make a
soul for God You are my special
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, my love's the guy
No, no, no, it's always c'mon, right,
day It should make you
die you are all love And
that's it for God You are
my special We are special
we're talking about satoru Kinji here
what proof do you have for me to believe
you sorry but i don't have any the only
thing i can offer is the very fact that i'm
here i was killed on october 19th by the
special great cursed spirit called mahito
what's here is no more than the insurance
i left when i was still alive this was my
contingency plan i had no choice but to
set its condition to activate after satoru
gojo has been sealed to decrease the risk
of a malfunction i limited the position of
these puppets to three
locations yuji itadori
was the least likely jujutsu high sorcerer
to leak any information and may may given
the situation i'm now
certain you're in the
clear too. Why's that?
Because someone as skilled at intelligence
gathering as you was dispatched
here to Meiji Shrine Station instead
of acting in the shadows at Shibuya.
And Itadori wasn't even a part of
Jujutsu Society until several months ago.
Maybe, but what if I was just simply
refusing to follow orders?
Besides, I've been the one stopping
Itadori from going straight
to Shibuya this whole time.
Even though we were
ordered to be on standby.
Then explain
Why is a curse user currently
heading your way to kill you?
One and two.
I count two of them.
Tell me, Itadori, which is stronger,
these two approaching now or the
cursed spirit you fought earlier?
They're probably stronger
than that grasshopper.
Apparently,
the cursed spirit Itadori thought
was able to speak human languages,
so it was semi-first-grade
or higher at least.
And things like that are now
crawling out of the woodwork.
I have to wonder where they've
been hiding this whole time.
Let's go ahead and ignore
the cursed users for now.
We need to confirm Gojo's status first.
Don't.
The situation in Shibuya
has already changed.
Their barrier techniques are
several degrees better than ours.
There are currently four
veils lowered over Shibuya.
One, the veil-trapping civilians inside.
Two, the veil-trapping Satoru Gojo inside.
Three, the veil-barring
sorcerers from entering.
And four, another veil like one to
keep common people trapped inside.
And you're saying the area further down
these tracks is blocked by veil three.
That's right.
The sorcerers on standby are already
inside the veil, aren't they?
And you can't use cell
phones inside the veil.
And it looks like that's not all either.
I can't contact the assistant
supervisors waiting outside the veils.
Please, just follow my directions.
My contingency plan
won't last long. Please.
Meimei.
Hmm.
All right, tell us.
We'll listen to you.
Itadori, return to Meiji Shrine Station.
Then head to Shibuya from the surface.
Tell all the sorcerers there
about Gojo being sealed.
Convince them they must
collaborate to rescue Gojo.
Right.
Meili, create an opportunity
for Itadori to escape.
After defeating the curse users, I'd like
you to manage things out here for a while.
I don't know what moves
the enemy will make.
We'll adapt and respond.
By the way, they haven't frozen
your bank account yet, have they?
Ah.
If Satoru Gojo disappears,
the Jujutsu world and the human
world will both be upended.
I need you to please
stake your life on this.
I used to think it would be okay
if everything was destroyed.
I was the worst.
I know that now.
Hey, anything for me to do?
Follow whoever.
Fix this news!
Hey, everyone. Incoming.
You're Mei-Mei, right?
Go ahead and do your best.
I'll match you both.
Let's go!
Looks like you're all awake.
And now, for our next... Huh?
What's wrong?
I hate this guy.
Looks like physical time
doesn't pass inside here.
Man, did I screw up or what?
This place is all kinds of bad.
Well, it'll all work out somehow.
I have faith in everyone.
It's true, all right.
Even accounting for those
trapped inside the station,
the number of people there was quite low.
So let me get this straight.
The transfigured humans were lying
in wait inside the buildings,
and now they started attacking
the non-sorcerers, is that right?
Our orders are to stop standing
by and start attacking.
There wasn't much else we could do.
Our response is starting
to fall too far behind.
But I have an even bigger concern.
The veil keeping sorcerers out
that was lowered at the same time.
It has been a while now since
Satoru Gojo arrived at the site.
Why'd they choose now of all times?
Either something has happened,
or they needed to wait long enough for
this moment as part of their strategy.
All I can say for certain, these aren't
the types to face us without a plan.
I'll focus on the enemies
who lowered the veils.
You two, please rescue
all the civilians you can.
Yes, right.
Once you've confirmed the situation,
please exit the Vale again, Nita.
With the signal blocked inside,
we'll constantly need someone
on the outside working with us.
Specifically, I'd like
you to take on that role.
We'll do whatever it takes to establish a
communication network with
the assistant supervisors.
It should be possible if
we mobilize those off-duty.
Hey!
Oh, man.
Bullying the weak really
is the perfect job for me.
This is what you all want, right?
Yes.
Please hunt down all the
humans wearing suits.
You'll find them all standing
outside the veil's perimeter.
Aye, aye.
And I can go inside when
I'm finished, right?
What's this?
What's going on?
The seal is now complete.
However,
the Prison Realm still
hasn't finished processing
all of the information
that is Satoru Gojo.
We won't be able to move it for a while.
Score one for them.
Itadori, good news. Huh?
They can't move Gojo from where he
was sealed on floor B5. Why not?
Because he's Satoru Gojo.
Makes sense.
Let's encircle them.
We'll have sorcerers
follow the subway lines
into Shibuya from each
neighboring station.
Once the veil keeping sorcerers
out is lifted, we charge in.
Have sorcerers follow them?
But I can't get a hold of Ijichi.
Oh, what?
Hey, do you have any idea
who was sent to Shibuya?
Well, let me see.
Help me, please!
Today you call for me.
NANAMI!
Are you here?
Huh? NANAMI?
Gojo is in trouble!
He's been sealed.
He's been sealed. He's been sealed.
You two, change of plans?
We need to meet up with Itadori at once.
If it's true that Gojo's been sealed,
then it's over for every
human in this country.
Oh man, now they know what we're doing.
The sorcerers are going to
be coming here in full force.
I've decided.
I'll be staying behind.
What about all of you?
I'll avenge my younger brothers by
killing Yuji Itadori and Nobara Kugisaki.
Then I'll make my way to
Jujutsu High and release
the rest of my brothers
from their captivity.
I don't care about
Kugisaki. But we're turning.
Itadori into Sukuna.
Not my problem.
Jogo, calm down.
Honestly, I think I want
to kill Itadori too.
Mahito, you're not helping.
From what I could tell after
seeing Satoru Gojo in person,
now that he's sealed away for good, the
sorcerers and cursed spirits are even.
If Sukuna is resurrected,
we'll have a huge advantage and
victory is basically ours, right?
I suppose that's true. But then,
doesn't that mean we're perfectly capable
of winning with the forces we have now?
So let's kill Itadori.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Even if we lose Sook now, we're still
in a position to win the battle.
You're serious?
As serious as I can possibly be.
I don't need to be the one smiling
in the Wasteland a century from now.
As long as curses can live as
people, that's all that matters.
Sukuna isn't actually our ally.
We might even be the ones who are facing
greater risk if he does become resurrected.
But if Sukuna does get resurrected,
the age of curses is guaranteed.
We are not like the humans of today.
We do not fear death, and we follow the
path to our goals without falsehoods.
And that is the essence of us
older curses that those fakes lack.
You're wrong.
No matter how off-kilter or
inconsistent we've become,
we always act in strict accordance
with our truest desires.
That's what it means to be a curse.
Oh, when I said you were wrong, I
meant regarding what curses are.
I agree that the whole resurrection
thing is a good strategy,
and I really don't want
to fight you over it.
So how about we play a game?
If I find Itadori first, then
I get to kill him like I want.
If you find him first, you can give him the
fingers and let Sukuna regain his power.
And if I find him first,
I get to kill him.
Okay. Hey!
Oh, you want in too, Choso?
Of course, that's fine.
You're more on Jogo's side if
you had to pick, right, Code?
Or am I wrong?
I have to remain here to
watch over the prison realm.
So I'll abstain from the game.
I'm fine with whatever you do.
As far as I'm concerned,
Sukuna was always just the backup
plan in case the prison realm failed.
This is ridiculous.
All the sorcerers, including Itadori,
will be headed this way to
save Gojo, and we're arguing.
So all you have to do is wait here.
This won't be really a game.
Those cursed spirits are actually smarter
than the two of you give him back.
We cooperated with you fully and
kept dropping monkeys for you.
Now give us back Master
Gato's body like you promised.
Don't toy with Master Code
any further than you have.
Obviously, I'm keeping him.
I don't recall leaving either of
your heads empty, but maybe I forgot.
The next time you make a
promise with a sorcerer,
you should make sure it's a
pact that can never be broken.
Now be gone or is it your desire
to be killed by this body?
You'll regret this.
Regret? Huh.
Now what did regret taste like again?
NANAMI! NANAMI!
NANAMI!
NANAMI! Hey there.
Say hey, moron.
NANAMI!
Fushiguro! Kento dude! And who?
You really refer to NANAMI like that?
Code did?
To be more precise, the thing
that's living within Suguru Code.
Shibuya Station is in
Pandemonium right now.
It's full of those special grades,
the cursed spirits they brought with
them, the curse users tied to Code,
as well as transfigured
humans and normal people.
In that case,
it'd be faster to attack through the
subway from the neighboring stations.
But to do that, we need to find
a way to lift that veil first.
It's an emergency.
Please multitask.
Guess this isn't the time for complaining.
There are several things only a
first-grade sorcerer can manage.
I'm just going to step outside
and take care of this with Ijichi.
During that time,
I want you three to do something
about the veil keeping sorcerers out.
Ino.
Kusakabe and special first-grade sorcerer
Zenin should be inside this veil as well.
If you're able to meet up with them,
please relay this situation and
request their immediate help.
Thanks to Itadori's shouting,
I'm sure they already know.
Roger that.
Also, take care of these two.
Fright!
Ina?
Nanami is counting on me.
You two!
Before we start the mission, let me
make it clear how important this is.
Listen up!
Losing Gojo creates two major issues.
First, the collapse of the Gojo clan.
The Gojo clan is currently a
one-man team of Satoru Gojo himself.
There are lots of sorcerers who have
been saved due to Gojo's influence,
pride, and wimps.
Itadori, you're one of
those sorcerers, right?
Oh, yeah! Casual, huh?
All of those people he saved are going
to find themselves in some major trouble.
And in the worst case...
That brings us to Issue 2, the
collapse of the power battles.
All of the cursed spirits and
curse users who've been keeping
quiet because Gojo was around will
start taking action all at once.
Now, if the guys from
Issue 2 try starting a war,
while society is in disarray
from fighting over Issue 1?
we're gonna lose.
That's the futurist Nanami and I see it.
So what do you think happens if we lose?
I would imagine at the very least that
the age of humans would be over for Japan.
I see I've taught you well.
Now, let's go you guys!
The three of us will break that
bill before Nanami gets back!
Let's rescue Satoru Gojo!
Thank you.
Did you hear that, Awasaka?
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
They're leaking information
to their enemies.
What's wrong with that, old Ogami?
It's finally starting to feel real to me.
Satoru Gojo really has been sealed.
I'm getting excited.
I wonder what's going to
happen to this country now.
Nothing new will happen.
People will still curse,
be cursed, and die.
Did you hear?
They said Gojo's little Satoru was sealed.
Oh, my, I always thought that
would happen to that boy one day.
He was always flaunting his style,
acting like he was nothing
but leg below his nipples.
Next time, seance.
Code, did you hear?
The Gojo's little...